Meliodas and the others were attacked by the Holy Knights.
(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)＜聖騎士団の
襲撃を受けるメリオダスたち＞
＜ その戦いのなか メリオダスは
｢女神の琥魄｣に封印され➡
During their battle,
Meliodas was sealed within the Goddess Amber,
and Veronica, Elizabeth's sister, perished.
エリザベスの姉
ベロニカが命を落とした＞
＜更に
現れたヘルブラムによって➡
After Helbram appeared,
the Seven Deadly Sins were cornered.
追い込まれる 七つの大罪たち＞
＜ そのとき 封印を破り
漆黒の痣に覆われた➡
It was then that Meliodas broke free and
emerged with jet-black marks all over his body.
メリオダスが現れた＞
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)うっ 熱い… 体の奥が…｡
My insides... They're burning up...
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)
どうやって あの｢琥魄｣から…｡
How did he break out from the Goddess—
ザシュ！
えっ？➡
うわぁ～～！ くっ！
よ… よくも！
H-How dare you!
ドォーン！
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)ああっ！
うわっ！ うそだろ…
軽く振っただけで この衝撃だと!?
You've gotta be kidding me!
How could such a light swing be so powerful?
We're in trouble!
まずい！
Super Recovery Spell!
｢超回復術｣！
ボン！
Thank you.
助かりました｡
話が違うぞ！
This can't be happening!
｢女神の琥魄｣からの脱出は
不可能じゃなかったのか!?
I thought it was impossible to
break out of the Goddess Amber!
分かりません｡ しかし➡
I don't know.
But this feeling of extraordinary magical power...
あのただならぬ魔力の気配
あれは…｡
That's...
＜ これは いまだ
人と 人ならざるものの世界が➡
This is a tale of humans and beings from other worlds.
分かたれてはいなかった
古の物語＞
It is a story of ancient times.
＜聖騎士は かつて
他の三つの種族と共に➡
Long ago, the Holy Knights fought alongside three tribes to seal away the Demon Clan.
魔神族を闇に葬った＞
＜聖戦と呼ばれたその戦いは➡
It was known as the Holy War, and memory of it has long left the minds of the people.
時を経て 人々の記憶から
消えてなくなった＞
＜ だが 今再び 聖戦が叫ばれる＞
However, a new Holy War has begun.
＜七つの大罪を葬り去れと＞
The battle to banish the Seven Deadly Sins unto oblivion.
're
Those who wander looking for answers, those who question in confusion
samayoi tou mono mo tomadoi kou mono mo
Will go beyond all sin.
subete no tsumi wo koe
Episode 13
Disciple of Destruction
(ﾊﾞﾝ)ありゃ 相当やべぇぞ｡
(２人)あっ！
That thing is really dangerous.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)よう ジャリコ｡
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)ジェリコだ！
Yo, Jaricho.
It's Jericho!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)悪ぃな｡
ついでに回復させてもらったぜ｡➡
Sorry, but thanks for healing me while you two were at it.
You've got some nice stuff on you, like these Incantation Orbs.
｢呪言の玉｣なんて
いいもん持ってんじゃんよ｡
いつの間に…｡
なっ！ よそ見すんじゃ…｡➡
When did he—?
Don't look away!
くっ！
てめぇ マジに団ちょなのか…｡
You... Are you really Cap'n?!
ザシュ！
なっ…｡
ドドォーン！
(ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽ)メリオダス様…｡
Lord Meliodas...
(ﾎｰｸ)エリザベスちゃん 大丈夫か？
Elizabeth, are you okay?
ホークちゃん…｡ メリオダス様に
一体 何が起こってるの？
Hawk, what in the world
happened to Lord Meliodas?
分かんねぇよ｡ ありゃ
ほんとに メリオダスなのか？
I don't know... Are we even sure that's really Meliodas?
ドォーン！
(ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽ ﾎｰｸ)うわっ！
あっ｡ メ… メリオダス様？
(ﾒﾘｵﾀﾞｽ)くんくん… くんくん…｡
L-Lord Meliodas?
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)ん？ これは…｡ なぜだ？
Hmm?
This is...
What's going on? He should have been sealed within the Goddess Amber.
確かに ｢女神の琥魄｣に
封印したはずだが｡ ん？
Don't even bother.
Now's not the time to be fighting you.
やめておけ｡ もう お前との
喧嘩どころじゃなくなった｡
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)な… 何を…｡
Wh-What?
ドォン！
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)うっ！
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)その姿… チミは…｡
That appearance... You're...
ドゴン！
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)うっ！➡
ああ～… ごほっ！
もう一度 言い直していいかな？
Allow me to correct myself.
ズドン！
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)うっ！ ぐおっ！
ドカッ ドカッ ドカッ ドカッ…
ぐわっ！
バキッ！
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)ふん！
ギーラやジェリコとは どうやら
根本的に違うようだな｡➡
It seems you're fundamentally
different from Guila and Jericho.
いや～ 実に うれしい誤算だよ｡
Well, what a fortunate
miscalculation this turned out to be.
チミ はなから混じっとるね？➡
You... were mixed from the beginning, right?
この桁違いの魔力➡
This unparalleled power...
後付けで 魔神の血を取り込んだ
新世代の連中とは➡
You're on a completely different level from the others who drank the demon blood later.
まるで 物が違う｡➡
It's no wonder that the Goddess Amber couldn't contain you.
｢女神の琥魄｣では
封印しきれないわけだ｡➡
Well, that's fine.
まっ いっか｡ そんなことよか➡
More importantly, let's see
what you're capable of, shall we?
もうちょっち
試させてもらおっかな～｡
うほ～！
Oh ho!
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)
殺す気満々なこの感じ いいねぇ｡➡
This wild, murderous intent... How wonderful.
それじゃ こっちも それなりに
本気でやっちゃおうかな！
Well then, I'll have to get serious too.
ドォーン！
バキン！
ドーン！
あっ やべっ！
真っ二つにしちゃった｡
Eh? Damn, I accidentally split him in two!
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)ひょえ～｡➡
So those jet-black marks moved and protected you?
あの漆黒の痣が移動して
ガードした？➡
俺っちの
神樹の剣のひと突きを無傷とは➡
You're unscathed after a direct hit from my sword.
相当のもんだにぃ～｡
Quite impressive.
Well then, how about this?
なら これはどうかね？
Hunter Wisp!
｢狩玉｣！
Hunter Wisp
パチン
命中！ イエイ！
Bull's-eye! Yeah!
I see, I see.
なるほど なるほど｡
魔力そのものは 高まったものの➡
Although his power has increased dramatically, he has lost his ability to use Full Counter.
｢全反撃｣の能力は
失われてしまう… と｡➡
これは 理性を失うためか
もしくは 別人格の線も｡➡
Perhaps this is due to his loss of mental faculties
or because of an alternate personality.
研究の必要あり… と｡➡
Further research is required.
いや～ 実に面白い｡
Well, well, this is truly fascinating.
(ﾏﾙﾏｽ)
このとんでもねぇ魔力は一体…｡➡
Whose crazy power is this?
He's as strong as Master Helbram!
ヘルブラム卿の魔力と
いい勝負だっぺ｡➡
Guess'll be on mah way since I've gotta look after Guila 'n th' rest.
ギーラのお守りもあるし
行ってみっか｡
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)待ちやがれ｡
(ﾏﾙﾏｽ)ぬぬっ？
Wait just a second!
You plan to leave just like that?
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)このまま行くつもりか？
無抵抗の相手に➡
Why did you use your power on a defenseless opponent and an innocent civilian, you bastard?
無関係な民衆を巻き込んで
魔力を使ったんだぞ お前は｡
(ﾏﾙﾏｽ)あん？ 相手は
王国転覆を謀っとる大罪人だべ｡
That opponent was a criminal who was
plannin' on overthrowin' the kingdom, y'know.
Between someone who put herself in harm's way to protect a civilian,
民を 体を張って助けたあいつと➡
クソったれのダンゴ虫の
どっちが罪人だ!?
or the scumbag roly-poly who kills innocents, who's the bigger criminal?!
(ﾏﾙﾏｽ)
ダ… ダンゴ虫だと… わっととと！
Who're you callin' roly-poly?
≪ドシン ドシン ドシン
(ﾏﾙﾏｽ)なんだ この揺れ？ あっ…｡
ドシン ドシン ドシン
(ﾎｰｸﾏﾏ)ブゴ～～ッ！
(ﾏﾙﾏｽ)どわぁ～！
ドドォーン！
Well, well, this is truly spectacular.
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)
いやはや 実に すんばらしい｡
But you won't be able to defeat my Link power.
が 俺っちの｢同調｣には
勝てないのだよん｡
チミの仲間のバン君と➡
You might say it's a bit like your friend Ban's power.
似て非なる魔力
といったところかな｡➡
他人の魔力を勝手に奪う
彼の｢強奪｣も えげつないけど➡
It's not as dirty as his Snatch
that steals other powers, but...
俺っちの｢同調｣は 俺っちに
同意してくれた人間の魔力を➡
My power, Link, lets me take on the powers
of others who have allied themselves with me.
拝借することができるんだ｡➡
だから チミの魔力が
どんなに強大だろうと…｡
So it doesn't matter how strong your powers are!
ドスッ！
And that's how it's going to be!
というわけだ！➡
うっ！ ぐわっ…｡
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)
まさか 魔力が上昇している｡➡
Unbelievable! His power is still increasing!
これでも まだ
完全な状態ではないというのか？
He hasn't yet reached his final form?
Fine, then.
(ﾍﾝﾄﾞﾘｸｾﾝ)
しかたない｡ 私が 少し貸そう｡
I'll lend you a bit of my own.
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)ぬおぉ～～！
ふん！
バキン！
一瞬 どうなることかと思ったぞ｡➡
For a moment, I didn't know what was going to happen.
しかし あの暴走状態を一撃とは➡
But to defeat that rampaging Meliodas in one hit,
ヘンドリクセン聖騎士長
恐ろしい方よ｡➡
Great Holy Knight Hendriksen...
is an absolutely terrifying man.
七つの大罪も
これで めでたく全滅｡➡
Now that the Seven Deadly Sins have been merrily annihilated,
あとは 剣に メリオダスに➡
all that's left to complete my mission is to bring back Meliodas, the Princess, and the sword.
王女を連れて帰れば
任務完了っと｡
そんな…｡
ちくしょう… 残る戦力は俺だけか｡
No way...
Dammit! Am I the only fighter left?
(ﾎｰｸﾏﾏ)ブゴ～～ッ！
(ﾏﾙﾏｽ)しっ しっ！ しっ しっ！➡
Go away or I'll turn you into flattened pork!
のし豚にされたくなきゃ 消えろ｡
あっ｡➡
おい！
(ﾏﾙﾏｽ)ん？ ええ～!?
Now then, let's capture you
before we have another rampage.
さて 暴走される前に回収するか｡
Don't tell me... he's just going to get taken like that?
まさか
あいつ 本当に このまま…｡
メリオダス様｡ メリオダ…｡
Lord Meliodas... Lord Melio—
Quiet. You can still run, right?
(ﾊﾞﾝ)
静かに｡ お前ら まだ走れるな？
えっ？
(ﾊﾞﾝ)こりゃ やばすぎる｡
This is too dangerous.
へっ？
まさか メリオダス様を➡
Are you just going to leave Lord Meliodas here?
置いていく気じゃ…｡
ちっ！
えっ？ は… 放して！
L-Let go of me!
無事 逃げきれたら放してやるよ！
I'll let go of you once we get out of here alive!
I've never seen Ban this nervous before.
(心の声)≪ここまで焦るバンは
初めて見たぜ≫
That Holy Knight must be really dangerous!
≪あの聖騎士
そこまで やべぇってことか≫
グリアモール！ ベロニカ姉様！
Griamor! Veronica!
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)大罪人に お似合いの
ぶざまな敗走だねぇ｡➡
Fleeing in humiliation... How fitting for criminals such as yourselves.
でも 逃がしはしないよ｡➡
Too bad you won't be getting away.
As soon as I have their hero, I'll—
英雄を回収したあと
すぐに… ん？
ガン！
Oh, so you were alive after all,
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)な～んだ 生きてたの？➡
Serpent's Sin of Envy, Diane!
嫉妬の罪のディアンヌ｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)団長…｡
Captain...
Uh, hello?
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)ああ～ もしもし？
感動の再会のとこ悪いけど➡
I'm sorry for interrupting your touching reunion, but how about we strike a deal?
俺っちと
取り引きといきませんかね？
お前か？
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)こっちに 罪人と王女を➡
You.
If you hand over Meliodas and Princess Elizabeth, I won't lay a hand on you or your friends.
引き渡せば
チミや昔の仲間には 一切 手は…｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)お前がやったのか？
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)おっとっと～｡➡
Was it you?
本日のヘルブラム占い｡➡
The Helbram Horoscope of the Day:
It would be wise not to do anything rash and foolish.
愚かで 浅はかな考えは
起こさぬが吉｡➡
You won't be able to defeat my Link power with just your measly Gideon.
ギデオン一本じゃ
俺っちの｢同調｣にはかなわない｡
お前が 団長をやったのか!?
Were you the one who did this to Captain?!
(ﾍﾝﾄﾞﾘｸｾﾝ)
ん…｡ 撤退しろ ヘルブラム｡
Retreat, Helbram.
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)でも
メリオダスと王女の回収は…｡
What about retrieving Meliodas and the Princess?
Retreat immediately!
即時撤退だ！
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)了解！
Yessir!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)うおぉ～～‼
ガン！
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)｢大地の怒号｣！
Mother Catastrophe!
Mother Catastrophe
They're here!
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)来た｡
Retreat at full speed!
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)全速で離脱！
プゴォ～！ 何これ!? 何これ!?
What is this? What is this?!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)しゃべってねぇで
豚足を回転させろ！
Stop talking and keep moving those hooves!
プゴォ～！
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)
くっ！ これが 神器本来の力…➡
So this is the true power of a Sacred Treasure.
いや 神器により引き出された➡
No, this is the true power of one of the Seven Deadly Sins
being drawn out by a Sacred Treasure!
七つの大罪本来の力｡
Don't stop running! Move it like you mean it!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)止まんな 師匠！ 走れ～！
とんとことん とんとことん…｡
ガン！
ズドォォーン！
(聖騎士)｢同調｣が切れた｡
まさか ヘルブラム様が…｡
The Link was broken!
Could Master Helbram have...?
(ﾊﾞﾝ)なっ？ やばかったろ？
うん｡
See, didn't I say it was too dangerous?
Yeah...
≫(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)お～い！
あっ｡
Hey!
メリオダス様！
とんとことことこ｡
Lord Meliodas!
Yo!
おっす｡ うわっ！
ふふっ！
ぐはっ…｡
メリオダ…｡
Lord Melio—
バキッ！
うっ！
Now, we can call it even for the time being.
とりあえず
これで さっきの分は チャラな｡
Deal.
おいっす…｡
メリオダス様｡
Lord Meliodas!
悪ぃな｡
I'm sorry.
どうしたんだよ？
What's wrong?
メリオダス様 メリオダス様…｡
Lord Meliodas... Lord Meliodas...
なあ エリザベス｡
Hey, Elizabeth...
はい｡
パンツ はこうぜ｡
Yes?
Let's put some underwear on.
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)団長！
触るな！
Captain!
Don’t touch her!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)
それで キングも 傷は平気？
So, King, are you okay too?
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)ははっ…
あんまり平気じゃないかも｡
I don't know if I'd say I'm okay...
(ﾊﾞﾝ)かすり傷くらいで
大げさなんだよ｡
Quit making a fuss over a little scratch.
What?
なんだ!?
あっ！
グリアモール！ 無事だったのね｡
Griamor!
Looks like you're fine.
I'm a failure as a Holy Knight.
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)聖騎士 失格です…｡
あなたを守れという➡
I even disobeyed Lady Veronica's last order...
ベロニカ様の最後の命令にまで➡
俺は背いてしまった｡➡
to protect you...
But... But I...
でも… でも俺は…｡
ありがとう｡ ずっと
ベロニカ姉様を思ってくれて｡
Thank you. For always thinking of Veronica until the very end.
ペーネスの湖畔に埋めてあげて｡
My sister loved the shore of Lake Pernes, where we'd always play together
姉様が好きだった…➡
私とあなたと三人で
よく遊びに行った あの湖畔に｡
and where we share many memories. Would you please bury her there?
私は 必ず聖騎士たちを止める｡
I will definitely stop the Holy Knights.
止めて… みせる｡
I'll stop them for sure.
あなたは
いつの間に それほど強く…｡
When did you become this strong?
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ･回想)((びっくりした？
僕が こんな大きな女の子で))
Are you surprised? That I'm such a big girl?
No. I'm glad you're all right.
((いや 無事でよかった))
Hauser, take the old man and that roly-poly and run away right now.
((ハウザー
今すぐ そのおじさんと➡
ダンゴ虫 連れて逃げて))
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)((逃げる？))
What do you mean, run?
Or... do you still want to capture me?
((それとも
まだ 僕を捕まえたい？))
((ははっ｡ また会おうぜ))
Let's meet again. Until then, stay on your guard.
((それまで 誰にもやられんなよ))
Will he go back to the kingdom after this?
あいつ 王国に戻るつもりかね？
さあな｡ 聖騎士も
一枚岩じゃねぇみてぇだし｡
Beats me. At least now we know there's some discord within the Holy Knights.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)
それより 団ちょ～ 剣はどした？
Anyway, Cap'n... What happened to your sword?
えっ？ あっ 盗られちまったな｡
軽っ！
Guess it was stolen.
た… 大切なものじゃ
ないんですか？ いいんですか？
I-Isn't it something important to you? Is that okay?
全然よくねぇよ｡ 事態は深刻だ｡
It's not okay at all. The situation is dire.
あぁ…｡
でも➡
But...
エリザベス
お前が無事なら それでいい｡
As long as you're fine, Elizabeth, I'm fine.
僕は 無事じゃなくていいんだ？
What, so it's all right even if I'm not fine?
何言ってんだ｡
お前が 無事じゃないわけがない｡
What are you talking about?
There's no way that you're not fine.
I'm not fine at all.
俺は むしろ
無事じゃねぇ｡
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)君って 案外 タフだね｡
You're surprisingly tough.
くんくん… 豚肉 食いてぇな｡
I feel like eating some pork.
ダイレクトだな！
ふふっ｡
That's a bit blunt!
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)
ぐっ…｡ いや～ あと一歩➡
If I'd been just one step late in retreating, I would've been done for.
撤退が遅れたら やばかった｡➡
Well, at least we have the spoils
of the war, so I suppose all is well.
けど まあ
戦利品があるだけ よしとしよう｡
One of the keys to the revival of the Demon Clan. A fragment of the Coffin of Eternal Darkness.
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)魔神族 復活の鍵の一つ➡
｢常闇の棺｣のかけら｡➡
The day terror returns to Britannia is near!
ブリタニアに
恐怖がよみがえる日は近い｡
What did you say?
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)
なんだと!? ベロニカが死んだ!?
Veronica is dead?!
During the Seven Deadly Sins' raid on Byzel,
it seems she and Griamor met an untimely death.
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)七つの大罪による
バイゼル襲撃の際➡
グリアモールと共に
非業の死を遂げたらしい｡
バカな！
グリアモールが そんな簡単に…｡
Impossible! There's no way
Griamor would've died so easily!
Besides, how are we supposed to
report all this to Princess Margaret?
第一 マーガレット姫に
なんて報告するんだよ！
ドレファス聖騎士長は？
自室にこもっている｡
Where's Great Holy Knight Dreyfus?
He's shut away in his quarters.
≪キン キン！ キン キン キン！
(剣の訓練をする音)
ふっ！
てやっ！
ドカッ！
ぐわっ！
You want to go home, you say?
家に帰りたいなんて…｡
この訓練は
いずれ起こる聖戦のためなんだ｡
This drill is to prepare ourselves for the Holy War.
L-Let me return... to my home...
くっ…
帰してくれ 家に…｡ ぐわっ！
(聖騎士)
君たちは ただ黙して 従えばいい｡
You all just need to stay quiet and listen to what we tell you.
この数日で ヘンドリクセン派の
聖騎士が 数を増した｡➡
In the past few days, the Holy Knights in Hendriksen’s faction have increased dramatically.
その全てが新世代｡➡
And they're all New Generation.
ヘンドリクセン派と
ドレファス派➡
Hendriksen's and Dreyfus's factions...
均衡を保っていた勢力は
崩れつつある｡➡
Up until now they were even in power, but now that balance has crumbled.
これも 聖戦の前触れなのか｡
Perhaps this is another precursor to the Holy War.
んん～！ 朝の冷えた空気が
俺の肉を引き締める｡
The chilly morning air is tightening up my body.
Guess I'll do some training to make up for our last battle!
さあ
先日の激戦の反省点も踏まえ➡
修行でもするか｡ とんとこ！
ベロニカ姉様 どうか安らかに｡
Veronica... May you rest in peace.
いつか 私たちが過ごした
あのころのような➡
I will turn this kingdom back
into a place where laughter fills the air
人々の笑い声が響く王国を
取り戻してみせます｡
like when we used to have fun in the old days.
この命に代えても｡
Even if it costs me my life!
≫(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)大丈夫だよ｡
あっ｡
It'll be all right.
必ず 王国は取り戻せる｡
We'll definitely return the
Kingdom to its former glory.
君には 団長がついてるんだから｡
You've got Captain on your side!
もちろん 仲間もね｡
仲間…｡
Not to mention other comrades.
Comrades?
Yeah. We're comrades now, okay?
うん｡ 僕たちは もう仲間だよ｡
ふふっ｡
Are you making fun of me, King?
なめてんのか キング！
もっと 本気でやれ｡
Come at me seriously!
Do it like you want to kill me!
俺を殺す気でな｡
To kill you, huh? Why?
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)殺す気ねぇ｡ どうして？
I just wanna crush the Holy Knights and take
back the Kingdom as soon as possible. That's all.
一刻も早く 聖騎士をぶっ潰し➡
王国を取り戻してぇからだ！
えっ？➡
うわぁ～！ ううっ！
王国を取り戻す？
それは びっくり発言だね｡
Take back the Kingdom? That's quite a surprise.
I thought you didn't care
about other people's business?
人のことには
興味がないんじゃなかったっけ？
Aren't you the same way?
おめぇだって そうだろうが｡
ぷっ！
まあね｡ でも おいらには➡
Well, yeah...
But I do have a specific reason: to help out Diane. That's all.
ディアンヌの手伝いをするという
特別な目的もある｡
(ﾊﾞﾝ)それなら 俺もある｡
ん？
If that's the case, I do too.
We'll save the kingdom, and as a reward, I'll be taking the Horn of Cernunnos stored underneath it.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)王国を救って
報酬に 王国の地下に眠る➡
｢ケルヌンノスの角笛｣を頂く｡
あっ ｢ケルヌンノスの角笛｣？
Horn of Cernunnos? Isn't that a ceremonial artifact that lets you communicate with the Goddess Clan?
女神族と交信するための
祭器だろ？
What are you going to do with it?
そんなもの どうする…
あっ まさか！
Wait, are you—?!
ああ｡ エレインを
女神に よみがえらせてもらう｡
Yeah. I'm going to revive Elaine with the help of a goddess.
バン…｡
だから 続きだ！ 来い！
Ban...
That's why we should continue! Come on!
ちぇっ 認めざるをえないか｡
I guess I have to accept him, don't I, Elaine?
なっ エレイン｡ あっ｡
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)団長のこと 気になるんだね｡
You're worried about Captain, aren't you?
やっぱりか｡
おいらも 内心 混乱してるんだ｡
I thought so. I'm struggling with it myself.
団長のあの姿 あれは…｡
Captain's appearance... That was—
(ﾊﾞﾝ)それ以上 言ってみろ！
てめぇの歯 全部 たたき折んぞ！
Just see what happens if you keep talking! I'll smash every tooth out of you!
だ… だって バンだって…｡
んなわけあるか！
B-But... even you must know—
Like hell I do! There's no way
that he's the same as that monster!
団ちょが
あの化け物と同じわけねぇ！
There's no way that can be true.
そんなことは 絶対に…｡
あっ… バン｡
Ban...
(ﾊﾞﾝ)団ちょは
一緒に来いっつったんだよ｡
Cap'n said, "Come with me!"
生まれたときから ずっと➡
He said that to someone who had spent his entire life as an outcast.
どこ行っても つまはじき者の➡
To a shitty person living a shitty life!
クソみてぇな人生を送ってきた
クソみてぇな男にな！➡
Elaine and Cap'n are the only two people in the world crazy enough to accept a person like that.
そんな物好きの変人は➡
この世に
エレインと団ちょだけなんだよ｡
聖騎士たちが あそこまで
力を付けているとはな｡
I didn't think the Holy Knights
could gain such power this quickly.
この先
手を抜いちゃ戦えねぇってことか｡
I guess I can't hold back in fights anymore.
Sweet...
甘っ｡ ぷっ｡
捨てなきゃいけねぇのかな｡
Guess I should throw this away.
ドドォーン！
When the skies are crossed with shooting stars,
｢一天を流星が十字に斬り裂く時➡
Britannia will be visited by a dreadful menace.
ブリタニアを
至大の脅威が見舞う｡➡
It is an omen of the beginning of a trial of ancient origins.
それは
古より定められし試練にして➡
光の導き手と 黒き血脈の➡
A Holy War between the guiding hand of light and the bloodline of darkness.
聖戦の始まりの兆しとならん｣｡
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)団長…｡
メリオダス様…｡
Captain...
Lord Meliodas...
俺は約束する｡
I promise.
ずっと 一緒に戦ってきた
あいつのためにも➡
And for the person who
fought beside me for so long...
3000年 繰り返してきた
この戦いに➡
This battle that has raged on for 3,000 years...
今度こそ ケリをつける！
I'll put an end to it once and for all!
kimi no sonzai dake de sekai wa mangekyou mitai da
With just your presence, the world begins to look like a kaleidoscope.
hashiru kimi ni awase keshika wa irodzuku kara
The scenery fills with color as you run onward.
hora mata kimi no mae de namida wo miseteshimatta
Here I am, showing you my tears again.
nani ga attemo zutto hanaranaide kureta
But no matter what, you always stay by my side.
dareka wo mamorinuku to dareka ni tsumi wo tsukuru
By protecting someone, you create a sin for someone else.
ikiru hodo ai wo shitte kokoro wa tsuyokunaru
Learn of love, and grow stronger the longer you live on.
me no oku ni utsuru kako no kizu wa
But I'll drink down the scars from your past,
watashi ga nomihosu kara
Reflected in the depths of your eyes.
kimi no sonzai dake de sekai wa mangekyou mitai ni
With just your presence, the world begins to look like a kaleidoscope.
kuru kuru mawatte hikari ga sasu
Spinning around and around, shining its light.
kawaru kisetsu to kawaranai waraigoe
The seasons change while our laughing voices remain the same,
kimi wa omoide ni naranai yo
But you'll never be reduced to a memory,
koko ni iru kara
Because you're right here with me.
(ﾏｰｶﾞﾚｯﾄ)よく のこのこ
やってこられるものね｡➡
You've got some nerve to
show your face around here.
用件を言いなさい｡
State your business.
ベロニカが死んだ｡
≫ドン！(扉をたたく音)
Veronica has died.
It was the Holy Knights, wasn't it?
≫(ﾏｰｶﾞﾚｯﾄ)聖騎士ですね｡
No, the Seven Deadly Sins.
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)殺したのは 七つの大罪｡
≫(ﾏｰｶﾞﾚｯﾄ)ありえません｡
That's impossible!
Together with Elizabeth, who is
now considered a wanted fugitive,
彼らは すでに手配されている
エリザベスと共に➡
王国奪還を企てている｡
they're planning to seize the kingdom.
The day draws closer that you
people receive divine punishment.
(ﾏｰｶﾞﾚｯﾄ)あなたたちに
天罰が下される日は近いようね｡
No. The Seven Deadly Sins are the ones who shall die.
いいや｡ 死ぬのは 七つの大罪だ｡
≫(ﾏｰｶﾞﾚｯﾄ)
ギルサンダー 裏切りの聖騎士｡➡
Gilthunder...
The traitorous Holy Knight.
≫私は決して あなたを許さない｡
I will never forgive you.
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)マーガレット姫
あなたの呪詛など➡
Princess Margaret.
I shall consume all of your hatred.
全て この俺が 飲み干してやろう｡
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)あぁ～あ
喧嘩祭りも もう終わりか｡➡
来年は開催されないだろうなぁ｡➡
Next Episode's Report
もうちょっと
ラブヘルムやりたかったな｡
Guess the Byzel Fight Festival is over.
(ｱﾗﾝ)人は 過ちを犯しては
後悔を繰り返す生き物なのですね｡
I bet it won't be held again next year.
I would've liked to be Love♡Helm for a bit more, though.
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)なんだ お前？
おっと｡ あなたは どうやら➡
Humans are beings who frequently make mistakes and continue living in regret.
人ではないようだ｡
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)むっ!?
この 人でなし～！
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)ふざけんな このガキ！
Who are you?
Oops, looks like you're not even human.
(ｱﾗﾝ)次回 『七つの大罪』
｢本を読むひと｣｡
You're a miscreant!
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)だから 誰なんだよ お前？
フランス･パリの連続テロ事件で､
Don't mess around with me, you punk!
警察が行方を追っている
Next time, on The Seven Deadly Sins:
"A Person Who Reads."
２６歳の女について､
Episode 14
A Person Who Reads
I asked you who you are!
トルコの情報筋などは､
事件前にパリを離れ